vxgateway.com 2016-04-08

# VX GATEWAY : Cloud Payment Framework

##### Date Revised: 22nd February 2013

The term "our affiliates" refers to any one or more of VX Gateway (“VX”) and its companies related to VX by common ownership or control. The terms "we," "our" and "us" refer to each and all of VX and its affiliates. The terms "you" and "your" refer to individuals who have a relationship with one or more of us. The term "nonpublic personal information" refers to nonpublic information about you that we obtain in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. For example, nonpublic personal information includes information regarding your VX VXLOOP Account™ balance, including all debits and credits. The term "nonaffiliated third parties" refers to companies, other than our affiliates, that we do not own or control. 

**Why We Collect Information About You**  
We collect and use information about you only where we reasonably believe the information will be necessary or useful in providing you with the products and services you request from us, as well as to help us identify new opportunities to provide products, services and information to our members. The information we collect and use about you helps us to maintain the security of your accounts with us, improve the customer service we provide you, and operate more efficiently. 

**How We Protect the Information We Collect**  
We take great care to safeguard the information we collect and use about you. We permit access to the nonpublic personal information we collect about you to only those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. 

**Categories of Information We Collect**  
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others; and
  * Information we receive from a public source.

**Nonpublic Personal Information Policy:**  
Unless as otherwise stated herein, VX does not disclose nonpublic personal information about you except in the event of subpoena, Court order, or appropriate government authorities. 

**Categories of Information We Disclose to Affiliates**  
We may disclose the following kinds of nonpublic personal information about you to our affiliates: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;
  * Information about your transactions with us, such as your account balance, transaction history and parties to the transaction; and
  * Information we receive from a public source.

We disclose this information to our affiliates for a number of reasons, such as to assist us in administering your accounts or to identify products or services our affiliates may offer that may be of interest to you. Our affiliates observe the same practices we do to protect the privacy of information about you. 

**Your Rights Concerning Certain Information We Disclose to Our Affiliates**  
We are permitted by law to share information about our experiences and transactions with you (such as your account balance and your payment history with us) with our affiliates. We may also share “additional information” about you (such as information we receive from you on applications or from credit reporting agencies) with our affiliates. You may direct us not to disclose this additional information to our affiliates (see How To Opt out below.) Even if you opt out, we are allowed by law to share our experiences and transactions with you with our affiliates. 

**How Our Affiliates Use Information to Market to You**  
Our affiliates may use all of the nonpublic personal information we disclose to them about you to market their products and services to you.. 

**Your Right To Limit Marketing**  
You may direct us not to allow our affiliates to use your nonpublic personal information to market their products or services (see How To Opt Out below). Your choice to stop marketing from our affiliates will apply until you tell us to change your choice. 

**How to opt-out**  
You may modify your profile to direct us not to disclose additional information about you to our affiliates and not to allow our affiliates to use your non-public personal information that we disclose to them to market their products or services to you by doing the following steps; 

  1. Login at www.vxgateway.com
  2. Go to VXLOOP Menu & Select My Profile 
  3. Check the opt-out Of Emails box and Submit 

Your opt-out will apply to all VX account(s), however you will not be blocked from receiving critical emails from VX that we deem to be important to provide the service. Categories of certain non-affiliated third parties to whom we disclose information, and the categories of information we disclose, may disclose non-public personal information about you to certain non-affiliated third parties that perform services or functions on our behalf; including (but not limited to) financial data processing companies that process and maintain your account records for us, and financial institutions with whom we have written agreements to jointly offer, endorse or sponsor a financial product or service. We may disclose the following non-public personal information about you to those nonaffiliated third parties mentioned above:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;
  * Information about your transactions with us, including (but not limited to) your account balance, transaction history, and parties to the transaction; and
  * Information we receive from a public source.

When we disclose non-public personal information about you under these circumstances, we require that the non-affiliated third party agrees not to disclose your information, or use the information for any purpose other than those stated above. Other than as described in this section, we do not disclose any non-public personal information about you to any non-affiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. We do not disclose or sell non-public personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties for the purpose of marketing non-financial products or services. 

**Information concerning former and inactive members**  
If you happen to close your VX account(s) with us at some point in time, or if you become an inactive customer, we will adhere to the privacy policies and practices as described in this privacy policy notice.
